{
    "id": "66d0cc7ff53f43b3a1a602c52913b10e",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Wherever she went, people …………………. her looks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were admiring",
                "admires",
                "admired"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8acb759aa6a84dc193627f9f4df5c123"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you ……………………….?",
            "description": "In the present continuous tense, the verb form is be + ing. ",
            "answers": [
                "cry",
                "crying",
                "cried"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7cf06a05dac345d095b73f5a30952244"
        },
        {
            "question": "The spider …………………….. with a stone.",
            "description": "In the past simple, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "killed",
                "was killed",
                "had killed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ae59ce4dc3e0480b8258326640ed7118"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… by his rude behavior.",
            "description": "In the past simple, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "shocked",
                "was shocked",
                "had shocked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0afe5c63a86648e18f6d75c02c43a5e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cows and buffaloes ………………………. us milk.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "give",
                "gives",
                "are giving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "242bbec4701f4cbbb5c2c86673872239"
        },
        {
            "question": "My mother has always ……………………. my biggest fan and critic.",
            "description": "The present perfect is common with the time expressions always, ever and never. ",
            "answers": [
                "be",
                "been",
                "being"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b4bbf2a95054a7ca4767141fc37d395"
        },
        {
            "question": "The missing child ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has found",
                "has been found",
                "had found"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "57c2bdd8176f425883d444b527b25c01"
        },
        {
            "question": "Does she ……………………. what she is doing?",
            "description": "Use the first form of the verb after do, does and did.",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "known"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "760dc27714ad4fbf81b4d21a38b4c3a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind ……………………. me with this?",
            "description": "Use an ing form after would you mind.",
            "answers": [
                "help",
                "to help",
                "helping"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "15b29a53da424d35b5a08b4130d13998"
        },
        {
            "question": "She can neither ………………… nor ………………….",
            "description": "After modal auxiliaries, use the infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "sing, dance",
                "sings, dances",
                "sang, danced"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6dcaac4cb36c4349a8ea73535002049a"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ……………………. you do then?",
            "description": "Then indicates distance in time hence, use the past tense here.",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "do",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2842dc886df9416ca7c54271cee107e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Whom did you …………………… there?",
            "description": "Use the infinitive without to after do, does and did. ",
            "answers": [
                "meet",
                "met",
                "meet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6a80e951203d43ccba76f5001d7a7cd8"
        }
    ]
}